But we have to fight with the weapons that apply to the battlefields in which we're engaged.
And the most important ones are the social media.
So something that I get a lot on this Internet is people saying, you just be on this Internet.
You just have all the opinions on this Internet, but you're not really doing nothing, which is not true.
But I want to say that I believe that that is actually an attempt at reverse psychology.
We know that TikTok was just acquired by Israel.
And some people may not really understand why, but I have always said that it's because Israel misplayed their hand on October 7th.
And they thought that what was going to happen was that their continued manufactured consent of, oh, where the victims would happen as well in that instance.
And it didn't. It was disrupted because of TikTok, because the young people of TikTok said, now, hold on now, let's do some research.
And they ended up educating an entire world in a way that had not happened ever before.
They shifted the narrative.
And now they're trying to buy TikTok.
Well, they bought TikTok to attempt to do the same.
So anyone suggesting that social media is some like fruitless effort?
No, it is not.
Also, I want to remind you all that it has always been about getting to the people.
OK, like during the Gilded Age, when they were, you know, running for president and whatnot, they would pull up on the back of a truck and people would come and then they would talk to the people.
That's how people campaigned.
When Nixon was trying to convince everybody that he wasn't a crook, he went on the news.
That was the first time that that had ever happened, where like a president used the news to talk to the people, like use the TV to talk to the people.
Some of our favorites, whether it's Marcus Garvey or Malcolm X, stood on street corners to talk to the people.
This is the new street corner and it's international and it is cross-sectional and it is far more effective than any of these old fogies could have imagined.
Keep talking.
Get that rude, eh?